{
    "id": "cd4064c879764148b13850491fb7217a",
    "title": "Adverbs With Two Forms",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She always works ………………… ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "18d24ad5ec3a4eb7b723853abeb96497"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been following the happenings ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "close",
                "closely"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cf92c67bb8b049759ac0f8903c726a09"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… does any work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "25d8aac01efe42a9a566daf792c6e0dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………… refused to come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "flat",
                "flatly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f616a6b1cdf643babc60754b0558c955"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have …………………… different opinions on most subjects.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wide",
                "widely"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "29b7582f787643e6bce3a69b3ea1e633"
        },
        {
            "question": "Open your mouth ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wide",
                "widely"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "58e98da63f674137a0cf757245fa76d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He always arrives ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e4cb6dc297ba4c95932e084c4d83a56e"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ………………… amusing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "highly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3b7b3fc767e043229fcbeb2b5ede1d97"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ball hit me ……………………… on the nose.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "right",
                "rightly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "82c0d68aa5424fc794b05e8980dd8990"
        },
        {
            "question": "I thought you spoke to her rather …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sharp",
                "sharply"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e585e2832ec344c594db84722aad9530"
        }
    ]
}